A Guide to the Spotsylvania County (Va.) Deed Books, 1722-1794
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Spotsylvania County (Va.) Deed Books, 1722-1794
Library of Virginia
1146878-1146889
12 vols. (4376 p.) photostatic pages
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Use microfilm copies, Spotsylvania County, Reels 1-7.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in a transfer of court papers from Spotsylvania County.
Historical Information
Spotsylvania County was formed in 1720 from Essex, King William and King and Queen counties.
Scope and Content
Deed books, 1722-1794, of Spotsylvania County Court. The deed books record the name of the grantor and grantee, the residence of both individuals and the description of property being sold or transferred. All the volumes have indexes except E, J and N. The indexes contains the first and last names of the parties. It is arranged alphabetically from A-Z.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Additional Spotsylvania County Deed Book Records can be found on microfilm at the Library of Virginia. See A Guide to County and City Records on microfilm at www.lva.lib.va.us/whatwehave/local/local_rec/index.htm
Access Terms
Spotsylvania County (Va.). Circuit Court.; Spotsylvania County (Va.)--History--18th century.; Deed books--Virginia--Spotsylvania County.; Land records--Virginia--Spotsylvania County.; Local government records--Virginia--Spotsylvania County.
Contents List
- Deed Book, A., Pt. 1 1722-1729, 1146878
- Deed Book, A., Pt. 2 1722-1729, 1146879
- Deed Book, B. 1729-1734, 1146880
- Deed Book, D., Pt. 1 1742-1751, 1146881
- Deed Book, D., Pt. 2 1742-1751, 1146882
- Deed Book, E., Pt. 1 1751-1761, 1146883
- Deed Book, E., Pt. 2 1751-1761, 1146884
- Deed Book, E., Pt. 3 1751-1761, 1146885
- Deed Book, H. 1771-1774, 1146886
- Deed Book, J. 1774-1782, 1146887
- Deed Book, N., Pt. 1 1791-1794, 1146888
- Deed Book, N., Pt. 2 1791-1794, 1146889